sizzlingbit.com 2013-03-15

# Privacy Policy

_Last modified: October 21, 2011_

At SizzlingBit.com, the privacy of our visitors and readers is very important to us. Your privacy is guaranteed here.

We know that the privacy of your personal information is important. Below are the details on what types of information we collect and receive when you visit SizzlingBit.com, and how your information is protected. We never sell, share, release or rent your information to any third parties, ever.

### Information You Provide

SizzlingBit.com does not require any personal information. However certain services like, comments and feeds subscription, do requires a valid email address to verify if the user is legitimate or not. This information will never be used in a manner other than the purpose for which it was collected.

### Log Files

Like many other sites, SizzlingBit.com makes use of log files. When you access pages of this site via a browser, application or other client, our log files automatically record certain information. These log files may include information such as your web request, Internet Service Provider, Internet Protocol address, type of browser, browser language, referring/exit pages, the date and time of your request, and number of clicks to analyze trends and track movement of user on this site. These information are never sold, shared, released or rented to any individuals, third parties or any other organizations, and strictly kept for increasing the performance of the site.

### Cookies And Web Beacons

SizzlingBit.com never uses any cookie or web beacons to store information. However, to support SizzlingBit.com, we use third party vendors to serve ads based on your interest when you visit this site. These third party vendors may use technologies like cookies and web beacons to collect information such as your Internet Service Provider, Internet Protocol address, type of browser used to visit this site. These information are used to serve you geotargeted ads on this site. Google, as a third party vendor uses DoubleClick DART cookie to serve ads on SizzlingBit.com.

### DoubleClick DART Cookie

  * Third party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on a your prior visits to SizzlingBit.com.
  * Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to you based on your visit to SizzlingBit.com and/or other sites on the Internet.
  * DART cookie uses non personally identifiable information. And It does not collect any personal information about you, such as your physical address, name, email address or contact details.
  * You may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at this URL — <http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html>. (Alternatively, you can opt out of any third-party vendor’s use of cookies by visiting the Network Advertising Initiative opt-out page at this URL — <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>)

SizzlingBit.com has no access to, or control over these cookies, that are used by third-party vendors or advertisers.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of third-party vendors and advertisement companies for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions regarding how to opt out of certain practices. This privacy policy of SizzlingBit.com does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers, vendors, or sites.

### Changes To This Privacy Policy

Please note that this Privacy Policy may change from time to time without any prior warning. Also note that we may or may not notify the users of this site about any changes made to this Privacy Policy. However, this Privacy Policy will mention the exact date on which this policy was last modified.

### Further Information

If you have any further questions, queries or require any further information regarding this Privacy Policy or clarification on any of the clauses, please feel free to [contact us](http://www.sizzlingbit.com/contact/) through our website or email us at: _farzan [at] sizzlingbit [dot] com_
